resellerratings.com 2014-04-04

# Privacy Policy | ResellerRatings.com

Last Updated: Jan 16th, 2013

ResellerRatings.com provides this policy to provide you with information relating to how we collect, use and share information.

When we set out to make ResellerRatings.com the best shopping experience, we didn't want to settle on a generic one size fits all site. We wanted to build a site that speaks to the best deals and safest shopping experience for **you**. We respect your privacy and we do collect data on how you use our site and services in order to tailor it to your needs. 

ResellerRatings.com respects the privacy and security of its users. Our goal is to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. In order to achieve this goal, we sometimes collect information as you interact with our online services to understand what differentiates you from each of our millions of other users.

In order to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have prepared this statement disclosing the privacy practices for the entire ResellerRatings.com site. Additional terms and conditions regarding the collection and use of your information are also provided to you before you register. Here, you will learn what personally identifiable information of yours is collected, how and when we might use your information, how we protect your information, who has access to your information, and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

### Information Collected

ResellerRatings.com collects certain information from and about its users in three ways -- directly from the user, from our Web server logs, and with cookies.

  * User-Supplied Information: When you register for ResellerRatings.com, we may ask you for your name, email address, invoice numbers pertaining to online transactions, and some other personal information. The more accurate information you volunteer, the better we are able to customize your ResellerRatings.com experience.
  * Server Log Information: When you visit an Internet Web site, you disclose certain information about yourself, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the time of your visit, and the referring location (e.g., the Site or page that offered a link to a ResellerRatings.com page). ResellerRatings.com, like many other sites, records this basic information about visits to its site. 
  * Cookies: In order to offer and provide a customized, personal service, ResellerRatings.com uses cookies administered by an affiliate of ResellerRatings, to store and help track your information as you travel throughout the site. For example, we may use cookies to help remind us who you are and to deliver content and services based upon your account information. In addition, third party advertising networks may issue cookies when serving advertisements.

Cookies are simply pieces of information that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. The use of cookies is relatively standard and you will likely find them used on most other major Web sites. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can reset your browser either to notify you when you receive a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. You should understand that certain areas of many sites may not function properly if you set your browser to not accept cookies or if you reject a cookie. Merchants signing up for our services should also recognize that by displaying the ResellerRatings seals and/or widgets on their respective Web properties, merchant, on behalf of themselves and their users, authorize ResellerRatings and its affiliates to place cookies on browsers visiting the merchant-operated sites.

You should remember that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, such as in message boards, through e-mail, discussion groups, or in chat areas, your information can be collected and used by others. Although ResellerRatings.com tries to protect your personal information, ResellerRatings.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. You are also solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords you set up and/or any account information.

### How and When Information is Used

We use information in different ways to give you the best experience.

  * **User-supplied information:** This information is used for purposes such as personalization and verification.
  * **Web Server Logs:** This information helps us identify which areas of our site are of interest to our visitors. ResellerRatings.com also collects the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses of its visitors for the purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers.
  * **Cookies:** We use cookies to let users use our services more easily and to let us keep track of certain statistical information that helps us improve our site and offerings available by our affiliates. Cookies also allow us to save passwords and preferences for you so that you won't have to re-enter them the next time you visit. 
  * **Your Email Address:** We use your email address to send you information about your ResellerRatings.com account, such as your username and password, and confirmations of reviews that you have submitted to the site. From time to time, we may email you to let you know about new site features no more frequently than once per month but generally only a few times per year. Except as described in this Privacy Policy, your email address is never sold or otherwise provided to a 3rd party.
  * **Invoice Numbers:** When you submit a review of an online merchant to ResellerRatings.com, we ask you to provide an invoice number for your transaction with that merchant as evidence that you did indeed enter into a transaction with that merchant. Merchants have the ability to login to ResellerRatings.com to view invoice numbers submitted to our site by their customers for any given review of that merchant. Therefore any invoice number that you submit to our website is visible to the merchant to whom your review pertains, but not to any other merchants or users of our website. 

### How We Protect Your Information

The privacy and protection of your personal information is important to us. ResellerRatings.com does not make personally identifiable information available to any third parties without your permission or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. Any user statistics that we may provide to prospective advertisers or partners regarding your ResellerRatings.com usage are provided on an anonymous basis only and do not include any personally identifiable information about any individual user. 

Your access to some services and content is password protected. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. ResellerRatings.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. You should not disclose your user name and password to others. In addition, if applicable, you should remember to sign out of your ResellerRatings.com account or service at the end of each session. You may also wish to close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, despite our efforts to protect your personal information, ResellerRatings.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, or to or from our online products or services. You transmit all such information to us at your own risk. However, once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

###  Our Email Programs 

ResellerRatings.com sends the following types of emails to our users:

  1. **New user registrations:** When you signup for a free account at ResellerRatings.com, either to write a review to participate in our discussion forums, we send you a verification email containing a link. Click the link to verify and activate your account. Once activated, this email is no longer sent to you. You may receive more than one activation email reminder, but an opt-out link is provided at the bottom of these activation emails. 
  2. **Deal Newsletter:** You can choose to receive daily deals newsletters containing product specials found at various retailers. To receive this newsletter, you must opt in by inputting your email address into a form on our homepage. Then, you will receive a verification email to confirm that you want to receive the newsletter. Every newsletter that is sent out also includes an unsubscribe link at the bottom. 
  3. **Review Alerts:** If you are an online retailer, you can signup to be notified by email when reviewers post reviews to our site about your company. You can turn these email alerts on and off in the merchant administration panel that we provide to you. 
  4. When you write a review for a merchant listed at ResellerRatings.com, that merchant can post a public response in reply to your review. You will be emailed a copy of the merchant's response. Additionally, the merchant can contact you via our site, to send you an email via a web form. Your email address is not revealed to the merchant. If you wish to opt out of these types of emails, use the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email. 
  5. **Exit Survey Reminders:** Many Internet retailers participate in our exit survey program, which displays a popup window to the user after the user completes a purchase at the retailer's website. The exit survey window asks the user if they want to write a review of the retailer, and to enter their email address, if so. Then, one week later, we send a reminder email to the user, asking them to complete a review. Only one reminder email is sent, as part of this program, per the user's initial request.

### Who Has Access to the Information

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, ResellerRatings.com and its affiliates will not willfully disclose any individually identifiable information that has been collected about users to any third party without first receiving that user's permission, other than to provide its services. Personal information you include as part of your public user profile and other personal information you post on or through the ResellerRatings.com service as part of reviews is made publicly available and so can be accessed by nearly anyone who views your profile or reviews online. This includes your username, the biographical information and photos you include in your profile, and any personal information you may include in your postings of comments and reviews. ResellerRatings.com may disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or to protect the rights or property of ResellerRatings.com. ResellerRatings.com will use its best efforts to contact you if ResellerRatings.com is issued a subpoena or other legal process that requests your identity.

ResellerRatings.com may disclose personal information to affiliates or to third party vendors, consultants, and other service providers who are working on our behalf.

Also, your personal information may be disclosed or transferred to one or more third parties in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, restructuring or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to or by another company. When you are at the ResellerRatings.com site and asked for personal information, you share that information with ResellerRatings.com (or to affiliates and/or vendors providing services on behalf of ResellerRatings.com) alone, unless the service is offered in conjunction with another party. For example, some ResellerRatings.com services are offered in conjunction with another company. In order to provide such co-branded services to you, it is necessary for us to share your personal information with the company offering the co-branded service. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer of data by not using that particular service. If you choose to share your data with a provider of a co-branded service, you should understand that those providers may have separate privacy and data collection practices. ResellerRatings.com has no control over and accepts no liability for these independent practices. Each provider should more information regarding its privacy and/or use policies. 

### Third Party Advertising

We use Google and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site, other sites, and other interactive media about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Third party advertising companies may issue cookies when serving advertisements. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, third party cookies or other tracking technologies, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of these third parties to learn more about their privacy practices. If you would like to obtain an opt-out cookie from Google or other third-party advertising companies, or for more information about targeted advertising in connection with ad networks, please visit www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. Having an opt-out cookie means that the information collected from your website visits will not be used to target ads to you. You may have to obtain a new opt-out cookie for each browser you use and whenever you reset your cookies.

### How to Correct Inaccuracies

If you use another ResellerRatings.com service, we may send you a confirmation e-mail confirming your new account and/or service. The message will be sent to the address that you supplied us and will describe ways for you to change or delete the account information provided. Remember to keep the confirmation e-mail as it will also contain information that will help you in case you run into problems accessing our services. We welcome any questions or comments you have about Resellerratings.com: please direct them to our contact form. 

###  Updates to this Privacy Policy 

We may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we update this Privacy Policy, we will update the “last updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. Any changes to this Privacy Policy are effective upon posting. In the event of any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will use reasonable efforts to notify you of the change. 

### Opt Out of Email 

To stop receiving any kind of emails from ResellerRatings.com, contact us and provide your email address. Our Mailing Address to Contact Us: 

### Company Mailing Address:

ResellerRatings.com  
6665 Delmar, Suite #3000  
St. Louis, MO 63130

Or faster yet, contact us asap
